Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
What's with you tonight?
You don't usually get that worked up with me.
Where does it hurt?
Nowhere.
I'll step out for a smoke.
Deputy Director Wang.
Hey, keep it up, you hear me?
You're a good drinker, too.
President Fan, looks like
you haven't had your fill.
Come on, let me keep you company.
Bet you didn't know,
when we set up the branch,
the location was my idea.
Some colleague wanted India,
said their meds were great.
Know what I told him?
I said, "You've only ever used
that Indian magic oil huh?"
Come on, let's have another toast.
How does it taste this time?
Still like rouge?
Not bad.
Kind of intoxicating.
There's still half a pack of it.
Take it and savor it.
You might end up liking it.
Without the matches, it really
seems to be missing something.
Uncle You, I got you a present.
A present?
Did I forget an anniversary?
Here, have some water.
If you'd forgotten our anniversary
and still wanted a gift from me,
I'd have to tie you up
and keep you as my present.
I'll take that.
Hang on.
This serum is amazing.
Last time I had a shoot the next morning
and my skin was a mess,
this totally saved me.
So, I bought one for you, too.
It's pricey,
but seriously perfect.
If it's pricey, keep it for yourself.
It's not like I need to be on camera.
I got paid for a painting model gig
a few months back,
Three hours made me what I usually get
for a month of magazine shoots in Hua Country.
- You don't like it?
- That's not it.
You're wondering if I posed nude, aren't you?
I figured…
you'd have your own fair judgment.
Can't you just ask me straight up?
Keeping it bottled and guessing all the time.
Doesn't that tire you out?
I just didn't want you to...
Feel embarrassed?
Even if I had done it,
you'd be worrying about my feelings,
not getting jealous, right?
Zhen Zhen, I think I should respect
you and your choices.
So…
You didn't?
Of course not.
I wouldn't strip for a few lousy bucks.
I was wrapped up tight from head to toe,
but I sat for three straight hours.
Three hours?
Must've been tiring.
Not really.
He just wouldn't open a window.
It's not breathable at all.
"He"?
Your employer?
Yeah.
Zhen Zhen, you're beautiful in my painting…
Zhen Zhen…
Lu Zhen!
Right, my employer.
Anything new from your out-of-town gigs lately?
Work has been smooth.
But some of the Hua people
who came to Thailand before me
kept bossing me around.
I ignored them,
so they teamed up to make things hard.
I'll have to see them
at tomorrow's celebration party.
I really don't want to see them.
Zhen Zhen, I dragged you to Thailand
and you had to restart your career here.
I'm sorry you've had to put up with this.
I don't feel bad at all.
I chose this.
It's not even some grand career.
Petty people are everywhere.
It's fine.
Being with you is what's important.
Then don't overexert yourself.
If you don't want to go to the party, skip it.
Now, how can we cheer you up?
I was pretty happy just now.
Then... as you wish.
[Episode 2]
Yolanda really goes hard,
drinks like she never cares her health.
She has to bankroll her precious
pauper-to-riches guy.
Anyone singing?
Come on, join in.
Oh, right.
We have a guy dating one of those right here.
Lu Zhen, you still dating that... director guy?
Does he give you ten grand a month to spend?
You...
Heat it in the microwave before eating.
Also, Zhen Zhen,
if you go to the party,
take this card.
You know the PIN.
No point arguing with these people.
I should be calm and composed, like Shu Lang.
Yeah, we're dating,
and it's going great.
I'm a grown and able man.
Why would I spend someone else's money?
I bet no one's spending on you.
Exactly, you're probably paying out of pocket.
We just think you could do better.
- Find another one, right?
- Right.
Sorry, something came up.
I'm heading out.
Oh, so you've got time to contact resources,
but not to hang with friends?
That's so transactional.
Lu Zhen, we agreed.
Whoever leaves first pays the bill.
- When did we agree on that?
- When we walked in.
Don't tell me you can't pay
and you're playing dumb.
Spent all your cash raising that man?
Don't go too far.
Careful.
Mr. Fan.
Yolanda walks out
and comes back with a total hunk.
Look closer, the watch is a limited edition.
I met this lady in the hall.
She said her friends were in this room.
Folks, I didn't walk
into the wrong place, did I?
No, no, this is it.
Thanks so much.
Zhen Zhen, what a coincidence.
You're here, too.
Mr. Fan.
What a coincidence.
Hand her to me,
I'll call her friends to get her.
Been a while since I've seen you.
Oh, you're Lu Zhen's friend.
Chat away, I'll take Yolanda.
Hanging out with your friends?
- Who is this?
- Yeah, but I'm leaving.
Mr. Fan, let's talk outside.
Since fate brought me to your door,
how can I leave without buying
a round for your friends?
Waiter, put the tab for this room on me,
and bring three more 5A sets.
Mr. Fan.
Be good.
Dang, landed himself a new sugar daddy?
Didn't see that coming,
Lu Zhen's got moves.
I'm Fan Xiao.
I'm probably a few years older than you,
so call me Brother Fan.
I'm especially happy
to run into Zhen Zhen again.
His friends are my friends.
A small token, hope you all have fun.
Thanks, Brother Fan.
- Thanks, Brother Fan!
- You're so generous!
Zhen Zhen's straight forward,
not like those scheming types.
If he does something wrong,
I hope you'll cut him some slack.
Don't worry, Brother Fan.
We'll take good care of him.
You're handsome and generous.
Zhen Zhen's lucky to have a friend like you.
Come on, bottoms up.
Cheers, everyone.
Cheers!
Cheers, Mr. Fan.
Zhen Zhen.
You're still here, Mr. Fan?
Thanks for tonight.
You didn't have to spend like that.
They aren't really my friends.
- I know.
- You know?
The second I walked in,
you were strutting like a little rooster.
I could tell something went down.
Wasn't I the last person you noticed?
I was just putting on a show.
Adds drama.
Careful.
Buying the booze was to embarrass them.
No one gets to bully my dear Zhen Zhen.
[You Shu Lang]
Need me to make myself scarce?
It's fine.
Hello.
Zhen Zhen.
Where are you?
Is the party over?
Almost.
I'm with a friend.
I'm still working late.
I can't pick you up.
A mosquito.
Got it for you.
Zhen Zhen?
The guy on the phone sounds anxious.
Hello.
I'm fine, don't worry.
A bug just buzzed me.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Who was that?
Mr. Fan, thanks for tonight.
I'll pay you back for the drinks,
but it'll take some time.
Also, I was on the phone with...
Lu Zhen, you still here?
Brother Fan, you paid so quickly
and now you're leaving me drunk and unattended?
Is that so?
My bad, then.
You were saying? Who was on the phone?
Oh, just family.
Family, huh?
They sure care about you.
Brother Fan, I'm drunk.
How you going to make it up to me?
Name it.
I'm dizzy.
Why don't you take me home?
I'm homophobic,
so keep your distance.
But...
Zhen Zhen's the only exception.
Mr. Fan.
My ride's here.
Thanks again.
I'm off. See you.
Hello?
Right now?
At the office building?
Got it,
I'll be right there.
President Fan.
What brings you here this late?
Heard everyone's working overtime
on my business plan.
I felt bad.
So, I brought milk tea
to treat the team.
This one's yours.
Thanks for the thought.
I'll take the rest up,
but I'll pass.
I don't like sweet drinks.
This shop's famous.
Won't you try a sip?
Sorry, President Fan.
Give me a second, I need to take this call.
Zhen Zhen loves Uncle You so much.
You're home?
Yeah. Just walked in.
Uncle You, I really, really love you.
That's the fifth time since you got in the cab.
Did you drink too much?
Tired of me already?
When I was wooing you, I said it even more
and you didn't mind.
Are you in a meeting and can't talk?
No.
I just don't want you feeling sick
if you overdid it.
I feel fine.
But I suddenly missed you.
Okay, I won't keep you from work.
Take care.
Sleep early.
Good night.
I bought these laboriously
and got snubbed.
President Fan, lend me a stick of "Rouge."
Hooked already?
Not exactly.
But I rushed down and forgot mine.
And that cup? I got it with all the add-ons.
Guess my flattery missed the mark,
and still can't buy a smile from you.
I'm hardly worth the flattery.
You are, because you're
my only friend in this city.
And my only entertainment.
Can I chalk that up to…
poor wording?
Any time I say the wrong thing,
treat it like that.
You're my only friend,
but I'm not your only one.
If you can't say it right, then don't say it.
You're missing the mark.
Did I hear that right?
You actually swore?
Where's your gentle, modest,
frugal, yielding code of conduct?
You know all that
and still mangle your words?
I curse, yeah.
It wasn't a hallucination.
And thanks for the treats
on behalf of the team.
Hand them over.
I'm heading up.
I was very clear.
You're my only one,
I'm not yours.
See?
It's late and someone's still messaging you.
Different relationships, can't compare.
What's so different?
That's my partner.
How can you compare?
Your girlfriend, huh?
Yeah, can't compete with that.
He's not.
Still not.
I'm good at spotting my own kind.
Working this late,
aren't you worried
your girlfriend will get lonely
and be swept away?
Or are you that confident
no one can steal her?
If something can be stolen,
the foundation was bad to begin with.
I've got work.
I'm heading up.
And the treats?
You bought them for the team.
It's better if you bring them up yourself.
Shows sincerity.
Fuck.
Bohai's leadership catches on fast.
They've already put You Shu Lang
on the project team.
Time to put the company on ice.
When You Shu Lang comes begging,
I'll refuse to invest.
I wonder if his standing will plunge.
The higher he's lifted, the harder he falls.
Come to think of it,
I've kept the project and him
dangling for over a month.
He hasn't reached out either.
President Fan?
Sorry, Mr. Huang.
You were saying Changling Pharma
is juggling research and revenue.
I thought it must not be easy.
We're the secondary industry
under Changling University in Hua Country.
There's state support,
but it's a drop in the bucket.
Otherwise, researchers like us
wouldn't be out hunting for investment.
I get it, the fact you flew
to Bangkok shows real sincerity.
Once I learned your firm
is led by a boss from Hua Country
investing specifically in Hua pharma,
I wanted to buy a ticket that instant.
Here are the hard copies
for the Honeysuckle Drink project I mentioned.
You can browse it anytime.
Thank you.
Mr. Huang.
To understand a product,
you have to start at the root.
Like this team highlight photo.
Interesting shot.
Mr. Huang, please tell me about it.
This one...
Must've been six or seven years ago.
I was leading a team on a project.
Days and nights blurred together.
We even won an award.
Back then, Changling University
had just one research center.
Every project was professor-led with students.
Most people in this picture were my students.
We were so young back then.
Director You.
You look great when you smile.
Many sins begin with a smile.
Shi Li Hua.
Fan Xiao!
Without you to get into trouble with,
I can't sleep alone at night.
Now that's what I call mangled wording.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Thought you were done with business.
Weren't you going to party around the world
like a pampered prince?
I have a whole pile of uncles and big bros.
Unless a plague or war wipes them out,
that heir seat will never be mine.
What else am I good for
but being a layabout prince?
Not like the Nanwa family with few heirs,
and you're outstanding.
You might just make a splash.
I've set something up for tonight.
Don't be late.
You just landed,
but you're already hosting a party?
[You Shu Lang]
Your phone's ringing.
Let it ring.
What was I saying?
Oh, the party.
You know, now that I'm back,
plenty of folks begged to pick me up,
but I gave that honor to you
and you alone, Mr. Fan.
Fine.
Tonight, I'll find you some fun.
Deal.
Director You, it's been a while.
Sorry, Shu Lang.
I was stuck with a few business partners
and neglected you.
You're a busy man.
I invited you on short notice anyway.
Sorry for the hassle.
That might be true of others,
but not for you.
We could reschedule.
You thought of me today,
so there's no way I'm rescheduling.
I wanted to have you to myself,
but my childhood friend flew back
and I promised to host him.
You'll have to bear with me.
Not at all.
You're being too polite.
Come, I'll introduce someone to you.
Mr. Xue.
Oh. Mr. Fan.
Heir to Ruixiang Chain Pharmacies,
Deputy GM Xue.
This is Bohai Pharma's
office director, You Shu Lang.
He's a new friend,
but it's like we've known each other for years.
An intro like that from him?
You must be someone special!
Shu Lang, one key task
for Bohai's Thailand branch
is securing shelf space in local pharmacies.
Whether you can break in and find a market
rests heavily on Deputy GM Xue.
Ruixiang's distribution network
is top-three nationwide,
mainly serving the Hua community.
Thanks for introducing us.
I heard about Ruixiang's market share
when I first arrived.
I didn't expect the one at the helm
to be so young and capable.
You flatter me.
His friend is my friend.
Come, first drink's on me.
Mr. Xue, I've been looking everywhere for you.
Won't you have a drink with me?
How could I not? Come, let's go top off.
- Come on, let's drink!
- Go on.
Don't waste the lady's kindness.
I'm off then.
Come on, drinks!
Please excuse me,
- I'm stepping out for a smoke.
- Sure.
What are you staring at, Xiao?
You've got a real serious face.
It's nothing,
Just something dirty.
Your idea of fun looks decent,
but man is he dull.
Not just because he's a guy,
but he's just…
boring.
He's hell a interesting.
A saint, really.
A saint?
With you, a saint is going to get skinned.
Give us a show later, yeah?
Sure.
Xiao You, it's a critical moment
for the funding.
What's Mr. Fan's stance, exactly?
As project lead,
you need to push,
stop dragging your feet.
Hey, this the suite up ahead?
Yeah, let's go.
Is the stuff you brought strong?
Don't worry, it's a fresh batch.
They'll feel heaven.
Come on.
Come on!
Come on, Mr. Fan!
- Let's go, Xiao.
- Come sit.
Everyone, have a seat.
Let me introduce someone!
This is our new office clerk, Xiao Wan.
- And this is… the director...
- You.
Right, Director You.
Xiao Wan, your job's like his.
Learn from him.
See how he handles a room?
Take notes.
Oops, me and my big mouth.
No offense, Director You.
You're not wrong.
Office work is service work.
You have to know the right move
for the right setting.
Xiao Wan, was it?
Since your boss wants you to learn,
I'll play teacher today.
To do a good job in service,
first rule is to stay sober.
If you get drunk,
who takes care of your boss?
So, office staff with no alcohol tolerance
shouldn't lift a glass.
Here, have some water.
Thank you, Director You.
Xiao Wan can hold her liquor.
She can take care of all bigshots and her boss.
Right, Xiao Wan?
Y-Yes.
That's more like it.
Put the water down.
Bring the liquor.
Hold up.
Drinking alone is boring.
How about...
playing cards?
Loser drinks.
I'm in.
Come on! Cards!
Should've started with that.
Fine. What are we playing?
How do we drink?
Texas hold 'em?
Deal. Shuffle up.
Damn it! Me again?
Hurry up.
Want Xiao Wan to feed you?
I've had four shots.
Fan Xiao had one.
Director You had two.
How many have you had?
Don't worry about me.
Xiao Wan's row of shots is untouched.
She must be skilled and lucky
since you picked her to train.
Come on, next round.
I'll deal this time.
Can't have you doing it all.
How could I trouble you for this chore?
Don't be so polite.
Xiao Wan lost.
Time to drink.
Wait.
Don't make a young woman drink alone.
Come, I'll drink with you.
Pop quiz.
If someone's drunk
and wants to do a cross-arm toast with you,
what should a hostess do?
Then let me be a know-it-all.
I'll teach you.
You can say, "That isn't convenient."
"However, we can swap glasses."
That way, you keep things professional
without offending anyone.
If a guy's halfway decent,
he won't push for more.
Got it?
Got it.
Cheers.
Sorry, all the good liquor went to waste.
- Maybe...
- There's plenty more.
Director You.
Make sure...
you don't spill this one.
You're a really good drinker!
You Shu Lang.
You sure are a gentleman.
But swapping drinks
for a lady one for one, won't do.
You're right, Deputy GM Xue.
Water?
Sorry.
I don't feel well.
I'm heading back.
Enjoy.
I'll take you back.
Thanks, but there's no need.
I've already called a driver.
I'll go with you.
Hot?
Want your collar loosened?
- I'll help.
- No…
No.
Shu Lang, are you thirsty?
Let me help you.
Shu Lang.
Let me.
Let me...
Stop the car.
What's wrong?
Don't turn on the light.
Park here.
Please grab a taxi back.
I'll pay triple the fare.
I drank too much.
Sorry for the scene, Mr. Fan.
Shu Lang.
There are no outsiders here.
Don't call me that.
If you say it again,
there'll be a penalty.
I'm uncomfortable.
Let me get out and take a walk.
I'll grab a taxi later.
I'll go with you.
Don't.
You have a fever?
You're burning up.
Let go.
I'm getting out.
You've been drugged.
The girl's drink,
there was something in it.
So, you swapped drinks to save her?
Maybe I pushed this too far.
Mr. Fan...
Could you… step out?
I said, don't call me that.
Or there'll be a penalty.
What… kind of penalty?
Mr. Fan.
Can you get out?
I might be a mess in a minute.
Fine.
Can't see…
Can't see a thing.
Damn, this is insane.
I'd already decided to stop playing games
when I dropped him off.
Mr. You, get some rest.
Thanks for the ride,
See you, Mr. Fan.
No man is hotter than you.
What did you say?
I said,
good night.
Good night.
I'm sorry about tonight.
You Shu Lang.
You asked me out.
Don't you have anything you wanted to ask?
I did, about the investment.
But don't worry about me when you decide.
I'm just an employee.
Whatever you decide,
I won't starve.
The project looks promising.
It's passed evaluation.
Next is locking business terms.
Trust my professionalism,
I won't throw my money away,
even if we're…
friends.
I won't rush an LOI,
but I'll pull your company's deck
back out of the rejection pile
and have the team reevaluate.
Well... Thanks.
How will you thank me?
Dinner won't cut it.
That isn't enough.
Mr. Fan.
What do you want me to do?
When I think of something,
I'll tell you.
Okay.
Want me to avenge you for tonight?
On who?
Ruixiang's Xue Bao Tian?
No need.
I'll handle it.
What's your play?
He's loaded.
I can't go head-to-head.
I thought you were a saint
who'd take the hit and swallow it.
Screw off.
Bye.
What?
Did I scare you?
Hardly.
Got the matches?
This cigarette really is pretty addictive.
I'm off, bye.
Damn it, why did I think
he was going to kiss me?
Fan Xiao, what the hell
is wrong with your brain?
Forget it.
Why am I so worked up?
It's just a porn flick.
Just another hardworking soft-core actor.
Zhen Zhen…
Fuck.
There it is again! Zhen Zhen!
You two really love each other, huh!